<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><description>For the love to art.</description><title>Forein’</title><generator>Tumblr (3.0; @forein-theme)</generator><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/</link><item><title>In Order to be Irreplaceable One Must Become DifferentYou might...</title><description>&lt;img src="http://40.media.tumblr.com/78cdea8020f04d0a2f2c08db1fe7735e/tumblr_ng042jTEE11s3zi6to1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;In Order to be Irreplaceable One Must Become Different&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might also be asking whether it’s possible that this is illegal for her to do this. Well, it turns out that it’s actually not &lt;i&gt;illegal.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the fashion industry, there’s &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;very little&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/b&gt;intellectual property protection. They have trademark protection, but no copyright&lt;i&gt; protection&lt;/i&gt; and no patent protection to speak of. All they have, really, is &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trademark"&gt;trademark protection&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It means that &lt;i&gt;anybody&lt;/i&gt; could copy any garment on any person in this room and sell it as their own design. The &lt;b&gt;only thing&lt;/b&gt; that they &lt;i&gt;can’t copy&lt;/i&gt; is the actual trademark label within that piece of apparel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s one reason that you see logos splattered all over these products. It’s because it’s:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;A lot harder for knock-off artists&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Harder to knock off designs&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;They can’t knock off the logo&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, the reason for this, the reason that the fashion industry doesn’t have any copyright protection. Is because the courts decided long ago that apparel is too utilitarian to qualify for copyright protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;They didn’t want a handful of designers owning the seminal building blocks of our clothing. And then everybody else would have to license this cuff or this sleeve because &lt;i&gt;Joe Blow owns it.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Lets wrap things up.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve came this far you’re propably interested in &lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/talks/johanna_blakley_lessons_from_fashion_s_free_culture?language=en"&gt;watching&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/talks/johanna_blakley_lessons_from_fashion_s_free_culture/transcript"&gt;reading&lt;/a&gt; further. We are really happy that you’ve came this far, this perfectly acknowledges that typography in this theme is on point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt from Johanna Blakleys TED talk called “Lessons from fashion’s free culture”. It’s a very interesting talk, we recommend that you &lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/talks/johanna_blakley_lessons_from_fashion_s_free_culture?language=en"&gt;give it a go.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109359071875</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109359071875</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 21:20:00 -0600</pubDate><category>fashion</category><category>fashion culture</category><category>copyright</category></item><item><title>Style is Whatever you Want to do, if You Can Do it with Confidence</title><description>An in­tro­duc­tory para­graph is a great way to sum­marise the con­tent be­fore ‘read­er’ re­ally...</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109350571557</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109350571557</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 19:40:00 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Give a Girl the Right Shoes and She Can Rule the WorldFashion,...</title><description>&lt;img src="http://41.media.tumblr.com/e33ae3951d2fcf8c9f5450b132a708cb/tumblr_newdz0Jfjb1qzh0vno1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Give a Girl the Right Shoes and She Can Rule the World&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fashion, whether you like it or not, helps you project who you are to the world. Because of fast fashion, global trends actually get &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;established&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; much more quickly than they used to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And this, actually, is good news to trendsetters; they want trends to be set so that they can move product. For &lt;i&gt;fashionistas&lt;/i&gt;, they want to stay ahead of the curve. They don’t want to be wearing what everybody else is wearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And so, they want to &lt;a href="http://clyco.co/buy-forein"&gt;move on&lt;/a&gt; to the next trend as soon as possible. The other one is: Is it an idea? Is it something that needs to freely circulate in a free society?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No protection. Or is it a physically &lt;i&gt;fixed&lt;/i&gt; expression of an idea: something that somebody made and they deserve to own it for a while and make money from it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Trying to define the problem&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem is that digital technology has completely subverted the logic of this physically fixed, expression versus idea concept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Nowadays, we don’t really recognize a book as something that sits on our shelf&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or music as something that is a physical object that we can hold. It’s a digital file. It is barely tethered to any sort of physical reality in our minds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And these things, because we can copy and transmit them so easily, actually circulate within our culturea lot more like ideas than like physically instantiated objects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt from Johanna Blakleys TED talk called &lt;i&gt;“Lessons from fashion’s free culture”&lt;/i&gt;. It’s a very interesting talk, we recommend that you &lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/talks/johanna_blakley_lessons_from_fashion_s_free_culture?language=en"&gt;give it a go.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109264278584</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109264278584</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 21:20:00 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Elegance is Good Taste Plus a Dash of Daring - C.SnowFashion,...</title><description>&lt;img src="http://40.media.tumblr.com/00d604ef4a72ee2d1c3c0b0cb4d8d684/tumblr_n8fm4dP7pp1qbhipzo1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Elegance is Good Taste Plus a Dash of Daring - C.Snow&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fashion, whether you like it or not, helps you project who you are to the world. Because of fast fashion, global trends actually get established &lt;i&gt;much more quickly&lt;/i&gt; than they used to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And this, actually, is &lt;b&gt;good news&lt;/b&gt; to trendsetters; they want trends to be set so that they can move product. For fashionistas, they want to stay ahead of the curve. They don’t want to be wearing what everybody else is wearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I tell you, there is &lt;b&gt;no rest for the fashionable.&lt;/b&gt; Every season, these designers have to struggle to come up with the &lt;a href="http://clyco.co/buy-forein"&gt;new fabulous idea &lt;/a&gt;that everybody’s going to love. And this, let me tell you, is very good for the bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now of course, there’s a bunch of effects that this culture of copying has on the creative process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Weitzmans take on plagiarism&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stuart Weitzman is a very successful shoe designer. He has complained a lot about people &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;copying&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; him, but in one interview I read, he said it has really &lt;b&gt;forced&lt;/b&gt; him &lt;b&gt;to up his game.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had to come up with new ideas, new things that would be hard to copy. He came up with this &lt;i&gt;Bowden-wedge&lt;/i&gt; heelthat has to be made out of steel or titanium; if you make it from some sort of cheaper material, it’ll actually crack in two. It forced him to be a little more innovative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt from Johanna Blakleys TED talk called &lt;i&gt;“Lessons from fashion’s free culture”&lt;/i&gt;. It’s a very interesting talk, we recommend that you &lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/talks/johanna_blakley_lessons_from_fashion_s_free_culture?language=en"&gt;give it a go.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109168032515</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109168032515</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 21:20:00 -0600</pubDate><category>plagiarism</category><category>fashionista</category></item><item><title>Which Fashion Brand has the Best Store?Some people believe that...</title><description>&lt;img src="http://41.media.tumblr.com/4eec388f649023945d98828e279d2f33/tumblr_ngfsc5lsFZ1u4r092o1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Which Fashion Brand has the Best Store?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people believe that there are a few people at the top of the &lt;i&gt;fashion food chain&lt;/i&gt; who sort of dictate to us what we’re all going to wear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you talk to &lt;b&gt;any designer at any level,&lt;/b&gt; including these high-end designers, they always say their main inspiration comes from the street, where people remix and match our own fashion looks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that’s where they really get a lot of their creative inspiration, so it’s both a top-down and a bottom-up kind of industry. Now, the fast fashion giants have probably benefited the most from the lack of &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;copyright protection&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; in the fashion industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are notorious for knocking off high-end designs and selling them at very low prices. And they’ve been faced with a lot of lawsuits, but those lawsuits are usually not won by fashion &lt;a href="http://clyco.co/buy-forein"&gt;designers.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is it even worth the time?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The courts have said over and over again, “You don’t need any more intellectual property protection.” When you look at copies like this, you wonder: How do the&lt;i&gt; luxury high-end&lt;/i&gt; brands remain in business?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you can get it for &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;200 bucks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;, why pay a thousand? Well, that’s one reason we had a conference here at USC a few years ago. We invited Tom Ford to come – the conference was called, &lt;i&gt;“Ready to Share: Fashion and the Ownership of Creativity”&lt;/i&gt; – and we asked him exactly this question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what he had to say. He had just come off a successful stint as the lead designer at &lt;a href="http://clyco.co/buy-forein"&gt;Gucci,&lt;/a&gt; in case you didn’t know. Fashion, whether you like it or not, helps you project who you are to the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt from Johanna Blakleys TED talk called &lt;i&gt;“Lessons from fashion’s free culture”&lt;/i&gt;. It’s a very interesting talk, we recommend that you &lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/talks/johanna_blakley_lessons_from_fashion_s_free_culture?language=en"&gt;give it a go.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109159487432</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109159487432</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 19:40:00 -0600</pubDate><category>tom ford</category><category>creativity</category></item><item><title>See by Chloé 2015 Pre-FallSee by Chloé is back under the Chloé...</title><description>&lt;img src="http://41.media.tumblr.com/f27469aa952fcbad66c0ea007931bf77/tumblr_nic3vybb9W1u1s06xo4_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Caption on photoset posts? This theme supports it all!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;img src="http://41.media.tumblr.com/56197ef86bea431c565007a0ff08d430/tumblr_nic3vybb9W1u1s06xo1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="http://40.media.tumblr.com/b956184eb59ae9dfc6ee625e706ed89f/tumblr_nic3vybb9W1u1s06xo3_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="http://40.media.tumblr.com/ad2708a3a9189e2d13367cd964a5db89/tumblr_nic3vybb9W1u1s06xo6_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Add comments to every photo you want.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;img src="http://41.media.tumblr.com/0f093395c57bbcf2ac0e567aa3c4cf8f/tumblr_nic3vybb9W1u1s06xo2_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="http://40.media.tumblr.com/03f05fbead5fd83480d6361f160e0ea2/tumblr_nic3vybb9W1u1s06xo7_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src="http://36.media.tumblr.com/044afb77f8d3bf6914270d213a470ec3/tumblr_nic3vybb9W1u1s06xo5_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;See by Chloé 2015 Pre-Fall&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;See by Chloé is back under the Chloé roof, and with that milestone comes a new design and a new logo: “Le Bisou” a heart inside a pair of lips&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Courtesy of See by Chloé&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109065454805</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109065454805</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 21:20:00 -0600</pubDate><category>runway</category><category>pre-fall 2015</category><category>see by chloé</category></item><item><title>The Difference Between Style and Fashion is QualityI am a...</title><description>&lt;img src="http://41.media.tumblr.com/0e09266a13424431d575f44e6ead2941/tumblr_mz3aolHWuo1qh9n5lo1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Difference Between Style and Fashion is Quality&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am a writer. Writing books is my profession but it’s more than that, of course. It is also my great lifelong love and fascination. And I don’t expect that that’s ever going to change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, that said, something kind of peculiar has happened recently in my life and in my career, which has caused me to have to recalibrate my whole relationship with this work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the peculiar thing is that I recently wrote this book, this memoir called “Eat, Pray, Love” which, decidedly unlike any of my previous books, went out in the world for some reason, and became this big, mega-sensation, international bestseller thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your elusive creative genius&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result of which is that everywhere I go now, people treat me like I’m doomed. Seriously – doomed, doomed! Like, they come up to me now, all worried, and they say, “Aren’t you afraid you’re never going to be able to top that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aren’t you afraid you’re going to keep writing for your whole life and you’re never again going to create a book that anybody in the world cares about at all, ever again?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt from Elizabeth Gilbert TED talk called &lt;i&gt;“Your elusive creative genius”&lt;/i&gt;. It’s a very interesting talk, we recommend that you &lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/talks/elizabeth_gilbert_on_genius?language=en"&gt;give it a go.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109057914088</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/109057914088</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 19:40:00 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Ultimate Top 10 Fashion Cities All Over The WorldIf you like...</title><description>&lt;img src="http://36.media.tumblr.com/b58d8386858e4b814670ea36ed831642/tumblr_ngvixagTxS1r3hbd2o1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ultimate Top 10 Fashion Cities All Over The World&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like coasting from city to city, indulgin’ your passion for fashion than you should take a look at those ten destinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yep, you guessed it Paris, followed by New York, Milan, London, Barcelona and Rome, are the most fashionable cities in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Paris&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paris is the capital and most populous city of France. Situated on the Seine River, in the north of the country, it is in the center of the Île-de-France region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://38.media.tumblr.com/5e8fc0a785dd7ca2ea14f1b456eb4e58/tumblr_ngwbgiIWzC1sptodbo1_500.jpg" alt="reblogged from mariaoohlala.tumblr.com"/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paris and its suburbs have a population of 12,292,895 inhabitants, making it the second or third largest metropolitan area in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;New York&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;is the most populous city in the United States and the center of the New York metropolitan area, the premier gateway for legal immigration to the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://31.media.tumblr.com/74a4d7f9fb9fc3c6e9457aef602ce66b/tumblr_ngw3ahHfjY1tsfm3lo1_500.jpg" alt="reblogged from myhipsterw0rld.tumblr.com"/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A global power city, New York exerts a significant impact upon commerce, finance, media, art, fashion, research, technology, education, and entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Milan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Milan is the second-most populous city in Italy and the capital of Lombardy. The city proper has a population of about 1.3 million its urban area is the 5th largest in the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=""&gt;&lt;img src="https://31.media.tumblr.com/5940234037fe42d14e02014757f4a955/tumblr_inline_nj3s2lwUat1smeijd.jpg"/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Estimated population of about 5,264,000. The massive suburban sprawl that followed the post-war boom of the 1950s–60s and the growth of a vast commuter belt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay, we are going to end here. It was actually a top 3 but you get how it all works and looks, right?&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108970755544</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108970755544</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 21:20:00 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Photo</title><description>&lt;img src="http://36.media.tumblr.com/6ae585b0c862ab3299e9d0c8b6252bab/tumblr_n7hz5ketJa1sn2thco1_500.png"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108963342734</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108963342734</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 19:40:34 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Be sure what you want and be sure about yourself.</title><description>&lt;img src="http://40.media.tumblr.com/122d037bc868be039d1bdc6248dd4c65/tumblr_mzscw3DStf1qh9n5lo1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Be sure what you want and be sure about yourself.&lt;/h2&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108882790713</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108882790713</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 21:20:00 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Chat with Support Team</title><description>Support Team: Hello! What can we do for you?
Olivia: I was wondering if support is provided with...</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108874563146</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108874563146</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 19:40:00 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Street Outfit Guide. Be Rad that’s Really What it...</title><description>&lt;img src="http://36.media.tumblr.com/3433905cd9ee6726a4c619bf9ecda1a3/tumblr_mvwnn9nurd1rnofv7o1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Street Outfit Guide. Be Rad that’s Really What it Takes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Landscape ecology concerns itself with how the stream and the meadow and the forest and the &lt;i&gt;cliffs&lt;/i&gt; make habitats for plants and animals. This experience and this training lead me to get a wonderful job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wildlife Conservation Society, which works to save wildlife and wild places all over the world. And over the last decade, I traveled to over &lt;b&gt;40 countries&lt;/b&gt; to see jaguars and bears and elephants and tigers and rhinos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But every time I would return from my trips I’d return back to New York City. And on my weekends I would go up, just like all the other tourists, to the top of the &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empire State Building,&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and I’d look down on this landscape, on these ecosystems, and I’d wonder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;How does this landscape work to make habitat for plants and animals? How does it work to make habitat for animals like me?&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d go to &lt;i&gt;Times Square&lt;/i&gt; and I’d look at the amazing ladies on the wall, and wonder why nobody is looking at the historical figures just behind them. I’d go to Central Park and see the rolling topography of &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Central Park&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; come up against the abrupt and sheer topography of midtown Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;History and the Geography in NYC&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started reading about the history and the geography in &lt;a href="http://clyco.co/buy-forein"&gt;New York City.&lt;/a&gt; I read that New York City was the &lt;strike&gt;first&lt;/strike&gt; mega-city, a city of 10 million people or more, in 1950. I started seeing paintings like this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those of you who are from New York, this is &lt;i&gt;125th&lt;/i&gt; street under the West Side Highway. (Laughter) It was once a beach. And this painting has John James Audubon, the painter, sitting on the rock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;And it’s looking up on the wooded heights of Washington Heights to Jeffrey’s Hook, where the George Washington Bridge goes across today. This is an excerpt from Eric Sandersons TED talk called &lt;i&gt;“New York — before the City”&lt;/i&gt;. It’s a very interesting talk, we recommend that you &lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/talks/eric_sanderson_pictures_new_york_before_the_city/"&gt;give it a go.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108793043634</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108793043634</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 21:20:00 -0600</pubDate><category>NYC</category><category>Empire State Building</category></item><item><title>Manhattan at 6am</title><description>&lt;img src="http://41.media.tumblr.com/cd2d1cd6a5f215278be2107bc6ed2845/tumblr_n8gm3yyEkY1s31u5eo1_r2_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manhattan at 6am&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108784584414</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108784584414</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 19:40:48 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Fashion is not just beauty, it’s about good attitude.</title><description>&lt;img src="http://40.media.tumblr.com/4f2335fcf797da9c3c8166ef2c4a149f/tumblr_n70oxrp44N1qh9n5lo1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fashion is not just beauty, it’s about good attitude.&lt;/h2&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108697082697</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108697082697</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 20:30:00 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>Audio</title><description>&lt;iframe src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fapi.soundcloud.com%2Ftracks%2F177881578&amp;visual=true&amp;liking=false&amp;sharing=false&amp;auto_play=false&amp;show_comments=false&amp;continuous_play=false&amp;origin=tumblr" frameborder="0" allowtransparency="true" class="soundcloud_audio_player" width="500" height="500"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108604597125</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108604597125</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 20:30:52 -0600</pubDate></item><item><title>"The only real elegance is in the mind if you’ve got that the rest follows."</title><description>“The only real elegance is in the mind if you’ve got that the rest follows.” - Diana...</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108508673549</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108508673549</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 21:20:46 -0600</pubDate><category>fashion quotes</category><category>quote</category></item><item><title>Brands be aware of COS. They got their advertising game on...</title><description>&lt;iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/103694372?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0" width="400" height="225" frameborder="0" title="The Sound of COS" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brands be aware of COS. They got their advertising game on point. Or fleek should I say.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108500182566</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108500182566</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 19:40:40 -0600</pubDate><category>video</category><category>ad</category><category>advertising</category></item><item><title>Style is a reflection of your attitude and personality</title><description>&lt;img src="http://41.media.tumblr.com/bd3e202e2cbaf81bd3b36de8162a4d60/tumblr_n0ut4fSy7T1sbglwmo1_500.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Style is a reflection of your attitude and personality&lt;/h2&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108406093344</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108406093344</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 21:20:00 -0600</pubDate><category>elegant</category><category>fashion</category></item><item><title>Runway Model About Her Genetics, Looks &amp; Fashion World Reality</title><description>Victoria’s Secret Model, Cameron Russell admits she won a genetic lottery. She is a tall, pretty and...</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108398631147</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108398631147</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 19:40:28 -0600</pubDate><category>story</category><category>fashion</category><category>runway</category></item><item><title>Buy this theme</title><description>&lt;a href="http://clyco.co/buy-forein"&gt;Buy this theme&lt;/a&gt;</description><link>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108283872067</link><guid>http://forein-theme.tumblr.com/post/108283872067</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 15:05:40 -0600</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
